export const chapter = "Chapter - 6: KNOWING OUR BODY ";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question: "What are the external parts of the body?",
          optionA: "Brain, lungs, stomach",
          optionB: "Eyes, nose, mouth, hands",
          optionC: "Heart, legs, chest",
          correctAnswer: "Eyes, nose, mouth, hands",
        },
        {
          question: "Where are the lungs located in our body?",
          optionA: "Abdomen",
          optionB: "Head",
          optionC: "Chest",
          correctAnswer: "Chest",
        },
        {
          question: "What is the function of the brain in our body?",
          optionA: "Pumping blood",
          optionB: "Helping us breathe",
          optionC: "Thinking, feeling emotions, decision-making, and memory",
          correctAnswer:
            "Thinking, feeling emotions, decision-making, and memory",
        },
        {
          question: "What does the heart do in our body?",
          optionA: "Helps us breathe",
          optionB: "Pumps blood around the body",
          optionC: "Breaks down the food we eat",
          correctAnswer: "Pumps blood around the body",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which organ is shaped like the letter J and helps in breaking down the food we eat?",
          optionA: "Brain",
          optionB: "Heart",
          optionC: "Stomach",
          correctAnswer: "Stomach",
        },
        {
          question: "Where is the heart located in our body?",
          optionA: "Right side of the chest",
          optionB: "Left side of the chest",
          optionC: "Middle of the chest",
          correctAnswer: "Middle of the chest",
        },
        {
          question: "How do lungs help us?",
          optionA: "Control body parts",
          optionB: "Pump blood",
          optionC: "Breathe",
          correctAnswer: "Breathe",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which organ is described as the pumping station of our body?",
          optionA: "Brain",
          optionB: "Heart",
          optionC: "Lungs",
          correctAnswer: "Heart",
        },
        {
          question: "What are the internal parts of the body?",
          optionA: "Eyes, nose, mouth",
          optionB: "Brain, lungs, stomach, heart",
          optionC: "Hands, legs",
          correctAnswer: "Brain, lungs, stomach, heart",
        },
        {
          question: "What is the main function of the stomach in our body?",
          optionA: "Pumping blood",
          optionB: "Breaking down the food we eat",
          optionC: "Helping us breathe",
          correctAnswer: "Breaking down the food we eat",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blank with correct option:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question:
            "The ____________ parts of the body, such as eyes, nose, mouth, and hands, are visible externally.",
          optionA: "Internal",
          optionB: "Hidden",
          optionC: "External",
          correctAnswer: "External",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The brain, being the most important organ, is responsible for helping us think, feel emotions, make decisions, and ____________ things.",
          optionA: "Forget",
          optionB: "Visualize",
          optionC: "Remember",
          correctAnswer: "Remember",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The lungs, located in the ____________, assist us in the process of breathing.",
          optionA: "Head",
          optionB: "Abdomen",
          optionC: "Chest",
          correctAnswer: "Chest",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The heart, positioned in the middle of the chest, acts as the ____________ station of our body by pumping blood.",
          optionA: "Filtering",
          optionB: "Pumping",
          optionC: "Digestive",
          correctAnswer: "Pumping",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The stomach, shaped like the letter J, helps in breaking down the ____________ we eat.",
          optionA: "Water",
          optionB: "Food",
          optionC: "Air",
          correctAnswer: "Food",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The function of the lungs involves inhaling air, allowing it to come into the ____________, and exhaling it back out.",
          optionA: "Lungs",
          optionB: "Heart",
          optionC: "Stomach",
          correctAnswer: "Lungs",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The internal parts of the body, like the brain, lungs, stomach, and heart, are not visible externally and are located ____________ the body.",
          optionA: "Outside",
          optionB: "Inside",
          optionC: "Within",
          correctAnswer: "Inside",
        },
        {
          question: "The heart pumps blood to ____________ parts of our body.",
          optionA: "Specific",
          optionB: "Random",
          optionC: "Various",
          correctAnswer: "Various",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The brain controls the functioning of ____________ our body parts.",
          optionA: "Some",
          optionB: "Most",
          optionC: "All",
          correctAnswer: "All",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The primary role of the stomach is to help our body ____________ the food we eat.",
          optionA: "Chew",
          optionB: "Break down",
          optionC: "Store",
          correctAnswer: "Break down",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question:
            "The brain helps us to think, feel emotions, make decisions, and remember things.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "Lungs are located in the abdomen.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "The stomach helps our body to pump blood.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The heart is described as the filtering station of our body.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Members of a family share a common family name or surname.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The primary role of the stomach is to help our body store the food we eat.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The lungs assist in the process of breathing by inhaling and exhaling air.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The father goes out for work and earns happiness for the family.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The mother's primary role in a family is to earn money for the family.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Members of a family celebrate festivals, birthdays, and special occasions individually.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
